
[
  {
"questionid": "5293",
"question": "The thickness of the wing is defined as the distance between the lower and the upper side of the wing at the...",
"choice1": "Most inner part of the wing.",
"choice2": "Thinnest part of the wing.",
"choice3": "Thickest part of the wing.",
"choice4": "Most outer part of the wing.",
"answer": 3
},

{
"questionid": "5294",
"question": "How is referred to a tubular steel construction with a non self-supporting skin?",
"choice1": "Semi-monocoque construction.",
"choice2": "Grid construction",
"choice3": "Honeycomb structure",
"choice4": "Monocoque construction",
"answer": 2
},

{
"questionid": "5295",
"question": "Primary fuselage structures of wood or metal planes are usually made up by what components?",
"choice1": "Girders, rips and stringers",
"choice2": "Frames and stringer",
"choice3": "Rips, frames and covers",
"choice4": "Covers, stringers and forming parts",
"answer": 2
},

{
"questionid": "5297",
"question": "A construction made of frames and stringer with a supporting skin is called...",
"choice1": "Honeycomb structure",
"choice2": "Grid construction.",
"choice3": "Wood- or mixed construction.",
"choice4": "Semi-monocoque construction.",
"answer": 4
},

{
"questionid": "5299",
"question": "What are the major components of an aircraft's tail?",
"choice1": "Ailerons and elevator",
"choice2": "Horizontal tail and vertical tail",
"choice3": "Rudder and ailerons",
"choice4": "Steering wheel and pedals",
"answer": 2
},

{
"questionid": "5300",
"question": "The sandwich structure consists of two...",
"choice1": "Thin layers and a light core material",
"choice2": "Thin layers and a heavy core material",
"choice3": "Thick layers and a heavy core material.",
"choice4": "Thick layers and a light core material.",
"answer": 1
},

{
"questionid": "5301",
"question": "Which constructional elements give the wing its profile shape?",
"choice1": "Rips",
"choice2": "Planking",
"choice3": "Spar",
"choice4": "Tip",
"answer": 1
},

{
"questionid": "5302",
"question": "The load factor "n" describes the relationship between...",
"choice1": "Thrust and drag.",
"choice2": "Drag and lift.",
"choice3": "Lift and weight.",
"choice4": "Weight and thrust.",
"answer": 3
},

{
"questionid": "5303",
"question": "Which are the advantages of sandwich structures?",
"choice1": "High temperature durability and low weight",
"choice2": "Low weight, high stiffness, high stability, and high strength",
"choice3": "Good formability and high temperature durability",
"choice4": "High strength and good formability",
"answer": 2
},

{
"questionid": "5304",
"question": "Which of the stated materials shows the highest strength?",
"choice1": "Carbon fiber re-inforced plastic",
"choice2": "Aluminium",
"choice3": "Wood",
"choice4": "Magnesium",
"answer": 1
},

{
"questionid": "5305",
"question": "What needs to be considered if permissible limitations were exceeded?",
"choice1": "The helicopter must be inspected by the pilot in command and if no defect is found, no appropriate entry in the aircraft technical log is necessary",
"choice2": "The helicopter must be inspected by at least two pilots licensed on the type, one of whom must be the pilot in command",
"choice3": "The helicopter must be inspected by a qualified engineer before the next flight",
"choice4": "The helicopter must be subjected to a duplicate inspected by two engineers",
"answer": 3
},

{
"questionid": "5306",
"question": "Reasons for dents in the helicopter structure are...",
"choice1": "Material defects or old colour.",
"choice2": "Intense erosion or high wear.",
"choice3": "Hard landing or excessive stress.",
"choice4": "Excessive engine rpm and cylinder defects.",
"answer": 3
},

{
"questionid": "5307",
"question": "What kind of hydraulic oil is used in aeroplane systems today?",
"choice1": "Mineral oil",
"choice2": "Vegetable oi",
"choice3": "Bio-oil",
"choice4": "Synthetic oil",
"answer": 4
},

{
"questionid": "5309",
"question": "The fuselage structure may be damaged by...",
"choice1": "Exceeding the manoeuvering speed in heavy gusts.",
"choice2": "Neutralizing stick forces according to actual flight state",
"choice3": "Stall after exceeding the maximum angle of attack.",
"choice4": "Airspeed decreasing below a certain value.",
"answer": 1
},

{
"questionid": "5311",
"question": "How is the nose or tail wheel usually controlled on small aircraft and motor gliders?",
"choice1": "By the steering wheel",
"choice2": "By the control column",
"choice3": "By weight movement",
"choice4": "By the pedals",
"answer": 4
}

]
